<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Common Services on FuSearch Playground</title>
    <link>https://fusearch.net/common-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Common Services on FuSearch Playground</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://fusearch.net/common-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Remove Image Background</title>
      <link>https://fusearch.net/common-services/removebg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fusearch.net/common-services/removebg/</guid>
      <description>Remove Image Background Remove background from image using artificial intelligence.
apiKey Image file: Reset Submit Response Status </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Scanner</title>
      <link>https://fusearch.net/common-services/docscan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fusearch.net/common-services/docscan/</guid>
      <description>Document Scanner Computer vision based document scanner, take a photo of your documents and frame it.
apiKey Image file: Reset Submit Response Status </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Phone Carrier</title>
      <link>https://fusearch.net/common-services/phonenumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fusearch.net/common-services/phonenumber/</guid>
      <description>Global Phonenumber Carrier Inquiry A telephone number is a sequence of digits assigned to a landline telephone subscriber station connected to a telephone line or to a wireless electronic telephony device, such as a radio telephone or a mobile telephone, or to other devices for data transmission via the public switched telephone network (PSTN) or other public and private networks.
Playground apiKey Region Code Phonenumber Reset Submit Response Status </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resident Identity Card</title>
      <link>https://fusearch.net/common-services/idcard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fusearch.net/common-services/idcard/</guid>
      <description>Resident Identity Card The Resident Identity Card Number, also known as China&amp;rsquo;s ID Card Citizen Identity Number is 18 digits in total, which is composed of a 17 digit body code and one check code. The sequence from left to right is a six-digit address code, an eight-digit birthdate code, a three-digit sequence code, and a one-digit verification code.
The checksum The Checksum is the final digit, which confirms the validity of the ID number from the first 17 digits, utilizing ISO 7064:1983, MOD 11-2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Card Number</title>
      <link>https://fusearch.net/common-services/bankcard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fusearch.net/common-services/bankcard/</guid>
      <description>Global Bank Card Number A payment card number, primary account number (PAN), or simply a card number, is the card identifier found on payment cards, such as credit cards and debit cards, as well as stored-value cards, gift cards and other similar cards. In some situations the card number is referred to as a bank card number. The card number is primarily a card identifier and may not directly identify the bank account number/s to which the card is/are linked by the issuing entity.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>